Good [music] one.
[music]
>> [music]
>> Hello guys. I am in Taiwan now. The
weather is so nice. This is just right
outside our hotel. It's like San Rio
themed.
We're heading to 7-Eleven now cuz I'm
hungry. We're dragging her along. I know
she doesn't want to come.
Penny roasted chicken and egg.
Family chicken and egg combination for
us already.
>> What?
>> You know like Japan like the you buy the
egg sandwich and then you get family
chicken and you combine it yourself.
>> Oh, I didn't know that.
>> Oh, what's semi chicken?
>> Seami chicken?
>> What's that?
>> Girl, I don't know.
>> Okay, I'm going to get this. This one
looks cute as
dark.
No, wait. It's milk. We got milk tea
flavor.
>> Garlic chip. Then we got two onigiri
pudding.
>> Okay.
>> Then we got drinks. This I got this na.
Okay. And she got another thea the
another na but recommended na. Okay.
Mine not recommended. Okay. [laughter]
>> I'm sure someone recommended.
>> Day one.
>> Day one. We are going to
>> Can you say the correct pronunciation?
>> Chan. Actually, I don't know. [laughter]
>> So, first we're [music] going to go eat
at J Chan apartment, which is a little
cute cafe with pastries.
>> I'm getting this one, guys.
>> [music]
>> This place is [music] so cute, guys. And
the lighting is so good.
Place
this So cute
like that.
>> No,
>> no,
>> no.
>> So cute.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Get this. Get this one.
Chinese. [music]
[music]
>> Oh, this is my heaven. Oh, it's quite
So cute.
A glowy pupp.
I think this is so cute, but I don't
know if it's 300 ringit worth.
We're at Samo now.
I really like this bag.
I need
it.
Hey guys, we just got back to the hotel.
I'm going to give you a haul of whatever
we got today. [music] We took two
photos. This one is like four pictures.
This is just a photo strip, a mini
keychain thing. So cute. We chose two
different pictures. We [music] cute ass
cookie shop. And I got a tin of cookies.
Sheer tinted stick in Dutch cocoa.
It's like a brownish tint. They had a
glown popup upstairs, so [music] I only
got a pair of pink socks. Summer on the
bag.
>> How cute.
>> Tomorrow we're going to
>> see.
>> Okay. Okay. Okay. Tomorrow we're going
to
>> see.
[laughter]
We are going to Simmoning today. This is
the outfit [music]
dumplings. You tell
soybean and milk tea.
Pretty
[music]
cute.
My DJI camera died, so I'm using this
camera. We're getting like Hello Kitty
snacks as souvenirs for our friends. But
I got this [music] pineapple cake for
myself because it's in the shape of a
Hello Kitty.
You getting the vitamin ones? Yeah.
>> She came for [music] Gina.
You want to be the cheaper one, right?
>> Wait 260.
>> So cute. This stray cat. Guys, time to
buy something. Buy something
at
Fried Chicken.
We at the Hello Kitty 7-Eleven now.
You want something?
>> I'm going to give you a haul of whatever
I got today. So, first I got this
pineapple cake and it's [music] in Hello
Kitty packaging. And then me and my
friend Adrina got this for our other
friend Janette at this famous bakery. I
got this brown sugar rice pump. And then
I got a pack of six of their [music]
famous pineapple cakes. And then I got
this at the red house. Got three
postcards.
And this place was really [music] cute.
Then I got this PopMart. I got this one.
I got this.
[laughter]
These are his panties.
>> It's like a mers. And then I diyed my
own shirt. Cute. [music]
>> Hey guys, today we're going to the
sweepy 7-Eleven. We're going to
>> what?
>> Hey, Sleepy 7-Eleven right now as the
first stop for breakfast.
I'm going to get this blueberry and
cheese sandwich.
Blueberry cheese sandwich and a scallion
salmoniri.
[music]
Two eggs.
>> Blueberry and cheese sandwich.
>> White G lemon cucumber.
Okay.
>> Raspberry and pistachio.
This is going to look like he's my
>> [music]
[music]
>> We just finished exploring the Taipei
Fine Arts Museum and we're heading to a
German Christmas market.
Yeah, same.
This is shaved ice and peanut and sesame
moji.
Looks so good.
We're heading to another Taiwanese
convenience stores. I think it's called
High Life. And we want to get the frozen
smoothies. This is the smoothie machine.
And you can choose your fruit packets.
What is that? Yen.
>> High.
>> What's this?
>> Blueberry and apple. I'm going to get
this kiwi
>> because she's
[laughter]
find out.
>> Okay, guys. Whole time from what I got
today, I didn't get much, but I got
really like cute purchases that I really
like. So, number [music] one is this I'm
wearing right now. It's from Topology.
So, I bought this like phone phone strap
attachment. [music] And then the second
thing I bought, I bought this Stushy
shirt. This is my first ever Stusy
shirt.
Woo! Woo! It says Taiwan [music] on it
with the logo. That's what I bought
today. But tomorrow, we're going to go
to Juan, which will be fun. So, I'll see
you guys tomorrow.
>> [music]
>> Okay, we want anything but these two.
No, like I actually got a big guys.
Oh my god.
>> Yay. Okay, I got the default. I got a
boy. The defa.
>> Look at this. So cute.
>> I stuck my moi on.
Look, there's fish in this photo.
>> [music]
[music]
>> It's good.
>> [laughter]
>> Okay.
I got to [laughter] go.
Okay,
[laughter]
go fast.
It's matcha ice mocha and it's a little
bit grainy.
6 out of 10. We've been waiting at this
cafe and going through pictures, waiting
for the sun to set so we can take
pictures.
>> [music]
>> So many people here.
>> We're heading to Raer Night Market now
and SA's not coming because she has
poisoning so she can't make it.
>> Look how beautiful this temple is.
Street Night Market.
sausage. Black sausage.
>> Bye-bye.
>> Bye.
>> Right.
Solid seven out of 10.
Getting
matcha and peanut
butter
soft.
Thank you.
>> Thank you.
>> Okay. So, it's [music] blueberry. You
guys take a shot.
[singing]
>> We are done at the Rahul Market. I think
that was the best market out of
everything in it.
>> Tell them. Tell them.
>> We are on the way back now. It's already
11:00.
>> We are late. Sophia is asleep.
>> Four night time.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Honey latte.
>> Honey latte. Cinnamon honey latte.
Pistachio white chocolate. Push batha.
Sundried tomato and olive and honey and
cream.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Thanks.
Crab samp and chicken.
We're at the famous [music] Taipei 101
Alley like photo spot.
Comfy check.
>> Bracelet from Jang Drama. Hair from
Adrenous Ker. Shirt from Jaffy. [music]
Skirt from Liinu.
Top from Korea. Bottom from Korea. Shoes
from Thailand. I'm very such country,
bro.
>> Nails [music] by Zoe. Isn't she cute?
>> Bag from Stan Noil.
>> Dress from Princess Polly. Jacket from
Yes Style and boots from Tao. So, we all
just got back to the hotel to get ready
for our nice dinner tonight. [music] And
we have to make a reservation. So, we
asked the hotel staff to help us do that
cuz we don't have Taiwanese phone
numbers.
Yeah.
Cool.
We just finished dinner.
So red so we can have more alcohol.
>> Hey guys, we all just got back from
dinner and we [music] showered and
everything. But today is actually our
last full day in Taiwan. And tomorrow
we're flying back at like 7:00 in the
morning. Let me [music] give you a haul
of what I got today other than one
thing. I got the gray color.
Look how freaking cute [music] that is.
Oh my gosh. But anyways, thank you guys
for watching my Taiwan vlog. I hope you
guys had fun watching, but I'll see you
guys in the [music] next video. Make
sure to like, comment, and subscribe.
Bye-bye.
[music]